Guide to the Rocky Chin Papers WAG.325
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III. Teaching, 1973, 1980-1989, 1995; 0.25 Linear Feet in 1 manuscript box.
  - Asians and the Law: Course Development, circa 1980s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asian American Studies Course Materials and Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Asian Americans, Civil Rights, and the Law Reader, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)